This is not a performance.
This is a session of treatment,
time-travelling,
emotional computing
and feeling the
materiality of platforms.
This is also a seance
of tenderness and solidarity
towards those
who are selling their emotionality
and sensibility,
those who are the slaves of rating.
And at the same time those
who are the gods born
from Google maps,
the gods of our metadata.
All that’s happening now –
this is not an opening or a performance
under the open sky.
This is a treatment session,
where the borders
between doctors and patients
do not exist.
We are simultaneously doctors
and patients.
We are kindly asking you
to be tender
with those who are here
and would come here in close future.
Our task is to share
our warm-heartedness with them,
to share this emotional labour
that is falling on their shoulders
when they put a smartphone
on a dashboard.
Brought by the platform,
we will unite under the grey sky
of a highway.
We can use this timeframe to relax,
feeling the warms of the bodies
who have been sitting at your place before
and will be sitting after you.
It will be our interfaces to enter
into protocols,
smart contracts of our feelings.
We will become dispersed bodies
of Platform Perplex.
Our session will last for 20 minutes.
The session will begin in 30 seconds.
I am concentrating on being relaxed
and happy in this present moment.
My attention on the highway sound is growing.
I like this sound, it’s peaceful,
deep and powerful.
I see the diamonds falling.
I am focusing on their form, its transparency.
Sharpness of their edges.
On the light that is lying on the diamonds.
I am enjoying this view.
Now I’m concentrating
on being aware of each breath.
My attention on the breath
is continuous.
My attention on  the breath as it begins,
and my abdomen starts to expand.
I continue to pay attention
as my abdomen rises and falls
with each breath,
like a person going high and low on a hammock.
Going high and low on a hammock.
Like a swing,
my breath slows down at each end.
I follow it all the way as it slows down,
and starts again.
I embrace my breath
with all my care and attention.
Thoughts stay in the background.
I enjoy the rhythmic rise
and fall of my abdomen;
I enjoy staying in the here and the now.
I have stopped running forward
and backward.
I am infinite as the loop of data traffic.
The loop goes circle-wise
always random and in different directions,
but never stopping.
My mind keeps producing thoughts.
I do not follow the thoughts.
I concentrate on my breath.
I am comfortable and at ease.
I feel my neighbour.
Frou-frou of her clothes.
I concentrate on every little detail.
I see how the data flow before me.
Data are fragmented.
All by pieces.
They travel through time.
With inhuman speed.
The speed is always changing.
Subtle frou-frou is the only trace
I can feel.
The wind gently kisses my arms.
I am at the beginning
and simultaneously at the end
of these flows.
I feel how those flows are leaking out
through the gaps between us.
Our breath is controlling the speed of data.
I think of a face of person
sitting next to me.
I focus on the eyes.
The eyes are blinking.
Our blinking is being synchronised
with leds of routers.
Routers that are controlling the data flows.
Fragmenting them
and building them on another level.
As we in this car decreasing
and increasing the gap between us.
We are all forming an office for the highway.
An emotional cluster.
An emotional cluster
without a permanent address.
Standing on a road split
between virtual and another virtual.
I am inside of a reservoir of computing
And at the same time
I am the reservoir myself.
We are all feeding the clouds
the same way
as we are heating the air
inside of the car.
My neighbour is breathing out,
I breathe her air in.
Breathing out
Breathing in
My ID-card is with me now
I get it out of my pocket.
I touch it.
I feel its materiality.
Shaggy surface.
Rounded edgings.
My neighbour has a biometrical ID.
I imagine how her fingerprints
are conveniently settled down
inside of a chip.
I imagine a leaf of Aloe Vera.
Its velvety lubricity.
I close my eyes
and imagine this chip and a leaf.
They are almost indistinguishable.
Two surfaces of the same shagginess
With the lubricants of our emotions
underneath.
Needles and pins on them.
And wetness inside.
Shagginess and wetness
blooming from the data-centers
and server rooms.
This bloom is an ambassador
of new tactility
of previously unknown citizenship.
Citizenship of territories of computation
that are fragmented
and being continuously integrated
by agile methods of software development.
I think of a driver as a platform worker.
As an ambassador of this territory
Cutting our desires
and forming our speeches
according to the pulse
of the traffic lights of our cities.
Here in the car the part of air
was warmed up by him or her too.
I see how my body borders
are becoming transparent.
I am afraid
and at the same time I feel relief.
I am opening up loops in my mind.
I am starting to feel no borders.
I am a reservoir of emotional computing.
My hands are shaking.
I am appearing here,
and simultaneously there.
My senses rooted in wires.
Wires that go to my neighbour
Through her transparency and shagginess
Fermenting and melting together
with all cloud services on our path.
I am becoming fragmentary
and noncontiguous.
How to compute this fragmentation?
How to  appear somewhere else?
Focusing on my breath
keeps me from getting lost in thought.
I notice sounds and skin sensations
without reacting to them.
I smile at disturbances
such as memories,
little itches and noises.
Smiling relaxes me. I feel content.
With each breath
I arrive in the here and the now —
I am sitting upright,
breathing comfortably.
My mind is peaceful,
my body free of tension.
I am calm and rested.
Calm and rested.
I feel at home
here under this highway.
Here
Under highway.